Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files: Subject Files MS 3009-RG 13.Series III
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Subject Files, 1926-2000; 774 Linear feet (774 boxes)
  - Press: United States: State: Georgia, 1949-1958, 1975-1988 (Offsite-box 2410, Folder 33)
  - Press: United States: State: Illinois, 1960-1976 (Offsite-box 2410, Folder 34)
  - Press: United States: State: Louisiana, 1961-1962, 1982 (Offsite-box 2410, Folder 35)
  - Press: United States: State: Michigan, 1953-1988 (Offsite-box 2410, Folder 36)
  - Press: United States: State: Mississippi, 1956-1965, 1982 (Offsite-box 2410, Folder 37)
  - Press: United States: State: Montana, 1952-1959 (Offsite-box 2410, Folder 38)
  - Press: United States: State: North Carolina, 1966-1982 (Offsite-box 2410, Folder 39)
  - Press: United States: State: Oregon, 1955-1964 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 1)
  - Press: United States: State: Texas, 1954-1993 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 2)
  - Press: United States: State: Virginia, 1958-1974 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 3)
  - Press: United States: State Capital Correspondents, 1965-1978 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 4)
  - Press: United States: Status, 1965-1986 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 5)
  - Press: United States: Stereo Review, 1975-1989 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 6)
  - Press: United States: Strike Newspapers, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 7)
  - Press: United States: Style, 1948-1993 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Sunday Newspapers, 1954-1991 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 9-13)
  - Press: United States: Sunshine and Health, 1954-1960 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 14)
  - Press: United States: Ta-Tz, 1931-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 15-29)
  - Press: United States: Tabloids, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 2411, Folder 30-31)
  - Press: United States: Tabloids, 1931-1986 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 1-2)
  - Press: United States: Tallahassee, Fla., 1945-1983 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 3)
  - Press: United States: Tampa, Fla., 1958-1967 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 4)
  - Press: United States: Tampa, Fla.: Times, 1951-1982 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 5)
  - Press: United States: Tampa, Fla.: Tribune, 1951-1993 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 6)
  - Press: United States: Taos, N. Mex., 1950-1959 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 7)
  - Press: United States: Teen, 1966-1993 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Tempo, 1953-1964 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: Terre Haute, Ind., 1939-1982 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 10)
  - Press: United States: Texarkana, Tex., 1958, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 11)
  - Press: United States: Texas City, Tex., 1963-1979 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 12)
  - Press: United States: Texas Monthly, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 13-14)
  - Press: United States: Texas Quarterly, 1961-1965, 1980 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: This Week, 1935-1989 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 16)
  - Press: United States: Throwaways, 1933-1993 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 17)
  - Press: United States: Time, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 2412, Folder 18-29)
  - Press: United States: Time, 1967-1982 (Offsite-box 2464, Folder 1-17)
  - Press: United States: Time, 1932-1966, undated (Offsite-box 2465, Folder 1-21)
  - Press: United States: Time: Advertising, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 2465, Folder 22-23)
  - Press: United States: Time: Advertising, 1962-1971 (Offsite-box 2466, Folder 1-3)
  - Press: United States: Time: Awards, 1962-1993 (Offsite-box 2466, Folder 4)
  - Press: United States: Time: Board of Economists, 1969-1992 (Offsite-box 2466, Folder 5-11)
  - Press: United States: Time: Board of Economists: European, 1980-1987 (Offsite-box 2466, Folder 12)
  - Press: United States: Time: Board of Economists: Pacific, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 2466, Folder 13)
  - Press: United States: Time: Time Canada's, 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 2466, Folder 14)
  - Press: United States: Time: Censorship, 1960-1990 (Offsite-box 2466, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: Time: Circulation, 1962-1993 (Offsite-box 2466, Folder 16)
  - Press: United States: Time: Covers and Cover Stories, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2466, Folder 17-25)
  - Press: United States: Time: Covers and Cover Stories, 1938-1985 (Offsite-box 2467, Folder 1-29)
  - Press: United States: Time: Cover and Cover Stories: Sports Jinx, 1951-1973 (Offsite-box 2467, Folder 30)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions, 1948-1988 (Offsite-box 2467, Folder 31)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: A-Z, 1943-1987 (Offsite-box 2467, Folder 32)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: Air Express, 1941-1944 (Offsite-box 2467, Folder 33)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: Atlantic, 1946-1991 (Offsite-box 2467, Folder 34)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: Australia, 1943, 1965, 1986-1992 (Offsite-box 2467, Folder 35)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: Canada, 1962-1993 (Offsite-box 2467, Folder 36-37)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: Canada, 1954-1965 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 1-2)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: Demographic, 1962-1991 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 3)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: Election Extra, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 4)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: European, 1972-1991 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 5)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: International, 1961-1992 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 6)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: Latin America, 1944-1965, 1991 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 7)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: Pacific, 1943-1989 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editions: U.S. Regional, 1960-1989 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editorials, 1973-1990 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 10)
  - Press: United States: Time: Editor's Letters, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 11)
  - Press: United States: Time: Education Program, 1963-1992 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 12)
  - Press: United States: Time: Effects of Stories, 1959-1991 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 13)
  - Press: United States: Time: Format, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 14)
  - Press: United States: Time: History, 1973-1993 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: Time: Imitations, 1964-1979 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 16)
  - Press: United States: Time: In Fiction, 1966-1982 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 17)
  - Press: United States: Time: Life Access, 1984 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 18)
  - Press: United States: Time: Man of the Year, 1943-1993 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 19-30)
  - Press: United States: Time: Parodies, 1955-1986 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 31)
  - Press: United States: Time: Prices, 1947, 1963-1982 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 32)
  - Press: United States: Time: Publisher's Letter, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 2468, Folder 33-39)
  - Press: United States: Time: Publisher's Letter, 1960-1983 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 1-24)
  - Press: United States: Time: Radio Program, 1942-1961, 1984 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Time: Radio Program: March of Time, 1932-1991 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Time: Readership, 1962-1993 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 27-29)
  - Press: United States: Time: Reprints, 1971-1985 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 30)
  - Press: United States: Time: Sections, 1967-1992 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 31)
  - Press: United States: Time: Sections: A-Z, 1967-1993 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 32-33)
  - Press: United States: Time: Sections: Behavior, 1968-1980 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 34)
  - Press: United States: Time: Sections: Business, 1962-1989 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 35)
  - Press: United States: Time: Sections" Economy and Business, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 36)
  - Press: United States: Time: Sections: Environment, 1969, 1989 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 37)
  - Press: United States: Time: Sections: Essay, 1965-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 38)
  - Press: United States: Time: Sections: Law, 1963-1974, undated (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 39)
  - Press: United States: Time: Sections: Nation, 1968-1990 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 40)
  - Press: United States: Time: Special Issues, 1974-1992. undated (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 41-44)
  - Press: United States: Time: Style, 1935-1992, undated (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 45)
  - Press: United States: Today's Health, 1938-1984 (Offsite-box 2469, Folder 46)
  - Press: United States: Together, 1956-1968 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 1)
  - Press: United States: Toledo, Ohio, 1957-1967, 1990 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 2)
  - Press: United States: Toledo, Ohio: Blade, 1930, 1952-1990 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 3)
  - Press: United States: Toledo, Ohio: Times, 1959-1975 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 4)
  - Press: United States: Topeka, Kans., 1933-1975 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 5)
  - Press: United States: Topsham, Maine: Maine Times, 1969-1988 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 6)
  - Press: United States: Town and Country, 1936-1993 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 7)
  - Press: United States: Trade Publications, 1936, 1953-1992 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Trans-action, 1964-1970 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: Transportation, 1956-1992 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 10)
  - Press: United States: Travel, 1956, 1977 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 11)
  - Press: United States: Travel Writers, 1956-1988 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 12)
  - Press: United States: Trenton, N.J., 1956-1992 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 13)
  - Press: United States: Trialogue, 1979 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 14)
  - Press: United States: Triumph, 1966-1976 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: True, 1948-1975 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 16)
  - Press: United States: True Story, 1936-1982 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 17)
  - Press: United States: Tucson, Ariz., 1965-1986 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 18)
  - Press: United States: Tucson, Ariz.: Citizen, 1961-1992 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 19)
  - Press: United States: Tucson, Ariz.: Star, 1949-1992 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 20)
  - Press: United States: Tulane Drama Review, 1964-1971 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 21)
  - Press: United States: Tulsa, Okla., 1931-1992 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 22)
  - Press: United States: Tuscaloosa, Ala., 1956-1957, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 23)
  - Press: United States: TV: Cable Week, 1970-1990 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: TV Guide, 1955-1993 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 25-26)
  - Press: United States: Ua-Uz, 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 27-30)
  - Press: United States: U.S. News and World Report, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2470, Folder 31-34)
  - Press: United States: U.S. News and World Report, 1950-1986 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 1-3)
  - Press: United States: USA*1, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 4)
  - Press: United States: USA Today, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 5-8)
  - Press: United States: USA Weekend, 1956-1991 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: USSR, 1956-1965 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 10)
  - Press: United States: USSR Information Bulletin, 1952-1956 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 11)
  - Press: United States: Underground Press, 1967-1992 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 12-23)
    Folder 16, which is supposed contain material for 1975, is empty.
  - Press: United States: United Mine Workers Journal, 1955-1977 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: United Nations World, 1946-1953 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Urbanite, 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Us (Paperback Literary Quarterly), 1969 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 27)
  - Press: United States: Us (New York Times; Mcfadden/Warner; Lorimar-Telepictures/Straight Arrow), 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 28)
  - Press: United States: Utica, New York, 1935, 1957-1977 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 29)
  - Press: United States: Va-Vz, 1934-1993 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 30-34)
  - Press: United States: Vallejo, Calif., 1965 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 35)
  - Press: United States: Van Nuys, Calif., 1973-1981 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 36)
  - Press: United States: Vanity Fair, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2471, Folder 37-39)
  - Press: United States: Vanity Fair, 1930-1984 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 1)
  - Press: United States: Variety, 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 2-4)
  - Press: United States: Venture (Cowles Travel Magazine), 1963-1966, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 5)
  - Press: United States: Ventures (Magazine for Entrepreneurs), 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 6)
  - Press: United States: Venture Capital Journal, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 7)
  - Press: United States: Vibe, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Viet-Report, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: VIP, 1975-1981 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 10)
  - Press: United States: Virginia Beach, Va., 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 11)
  - Press: United States: Virginia City, Nev., 1952-1967 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 12)
  - Press: United States: Virginia Quarterly Review, 1950-1958, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 13)
  - Press: United States: Vision/Europe, 1970-1979 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 14)
  - Press: United States: Viva, 1970-1978, 1992 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: Vogue, 1932-1993 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 16-20)
  - Press: United States: Waa-Wz, 1929-1993 (Offsite-box 2472, Folder 21-35)
  - Press: United States: W, 1970-1993 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 1)
  - Press: United States: Ward's Auto World, 1972-1992 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 2)
  - Press: United States: Ward's Automotive Reports, 1974-1990 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 3)
  - Press: United States: Washington Correspondents, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 4-24)
  - Press: United States: Washington Monthly, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Washington Post Weekly, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Washingtonian, 1931-1992 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 27)
  - Press: United States: Weeks, 1955-1975 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 28)
  - Press: United States: Well, 1971 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 29)
  - Press: United States: Western World, 1957 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 30)
  - Press: United States: Whisper, 1955-1963 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 31)
  - Press: United States: Wichita, Kans., 1934, 1973-1985 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 32)
  - Press: United States: Wichita, Kans.: Beacon, 1933-1980 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 33)
  - Press: United States: Wichita, Kans.: Eagle, 1959-1992 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 34)
  - Press: United States: Wilmington, Del., 1955-1985 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 35)
  - Press: United States: Wilmington, Del.: Journal, 1960-1989 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 36)
  - Press: United States: Wilmington, Del.: News, 1963-1989 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 37)
  - Press: United States: Wilmington, N.C., 1956-1984 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 38)
  - Press: United States: Winston Salem, N.C., 1963-1973, 1991 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 39)
  - Press: United States: Winston Salem, N.C.: Journal, 1959-1989 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 40)
  - Press: United States: Winston Salem, N.C.: Twin City Sentinel, 1949-1951, 1985 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 41)
  - Press: United States: Wisdom, 1955-1964 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 42)
  - Press: United States: Woman, 1971-1991 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 43)
  - Press: United States: Woman, The, 1972-1990 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 44)
  - Press: United States: Woman's Day, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 2473, Folder 45)
  - Press: United States: Woman's Day, 1937-1979 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 1-2)
  - Press: United States: Woman's Home Companion, 1936-1988 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 3)
  - Press: United States: Women's Newspapers, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 4)
  - Press: United States: Women's Wear Daily, 1942-1992 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 5-7)
  - Press: United States: Worcester, Mass., 1959-1991 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 8)
  - Press: United States: Working Woman, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 9)
  - Press: United States: World, 1953-1986 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 10-12)
  - Press: United States: World Tennis, 1953-1991 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 13)
  - Press: United States: Worship, 1963-1966 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 14)
  - Press: United States: X, 1971-1975, 1991 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 15)
  - Press: United States: X-Ray, 1942 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 16)
  - Press: United States: Ya-Yz, 1950-1993 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 17-19)
  - Press: United States: Yachting, 1953-1984 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 20)
  - Press: United States: Yale Law Journal, 1961-1992 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 21)
  - Press: United States: Yale Literary Magazine, 1955-1987 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 22)
  - Press: United States: Yale Review, 1954-1992 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 23)
  - Press: United States: Yankee, 1967-1989 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 24)
  - Press: United States: Yellow Sheet, 1974-1981 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 25)
  - Press: United States: Youth's Companion, 1956-1988 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 26)
  - Press: United States: Z, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 27)
  - Press: Uruguay, 1946-1990 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 28)
  - Press: Uses, 1964-1993 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 29)
  - Press: Vatican City, 1956-1985 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 30)
  - Press: Vatican City: Latinitas, 1953-1959 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 31)
  - Press: Vatican City: Osservatore della Domenica, 1956-1990 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 32)
  - Press: Vatican City: Osservatore Romano, 1930-1992 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 33-40)
  - Press: Vatican City: Services and Syndicates, 1973 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 41)
  - Press: Venezuela, 1961-1985 (Offsite-box 2474, Folder 42-43)
  - Press: Venezuela, 1950-1960 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 1)
  - Press: Venezuela: A-Z, 1948-1992 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 2)
  - Press: Venezuela: Associations, 1959 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 3)
  - Press: Venezuela: Services and Syndicate, 1980 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 4)
  - Press: Viet Nam, 1955-1989 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 5-7)
  - Press: Viet Nam: A, 1970 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 8)
  - Press: Viet Nam: Associations, 1956-1975 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 9)
  - Press: Viet Nam: B-F, 1957-1990 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 10-13)
    There is no folder for the letter E.
  - Press: Viet Nam: Giai Phong, 1971-1976 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 14)
  - Press: Viet Nam: H-N, 1955-1975 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 15-19)
    There are no folders for letters I or K.
  - Press: Viet Nam: Nhan Dan, 1964-1987 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 20-21)
  - Press: Viet Nam: Nhan Van, 1957-1980 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 22)
  - Press: Viet Nam: P-S, 1961-1986 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 23-26)
  - Press: Viet Nam: Saigon Daily News, 1963-1969 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 27)
  - Press: Viet Nam: Saigon Post, 1965-1975 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 28)
  - Press: Viet Nam: Services and Syndicates, 1960-1980 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 29)
  - Press: Viet Nam: T, 1960-1988 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 30)
  - Press: Viet Nam: Times of Viet Nam, 1963 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 31)
  - Press: Viet Nam: U-Y, 1963-1989 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 32-35)
    No folders for letters W or Z.
  - Press: Virgin Islands, 1953-1981 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 36)
  - Press: West Indies, Great Britain, 1957, 1976 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 37)
  - Press: Windward Islands, 1957 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 38)
  - Press: Yemen, 1963-1992 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 39)
  - Press: Yugoslavia, 1950-1993 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 40-41)
  - Press: Yugoslavia: A-Z, 1950-1993 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 42-43)
  - Press: Yugoslavia: Associations, 1959, 1969 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 44)
  - Press: Yugoslavia: Borba, 1951-1988 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 45)
  - Press: Yugoslavia: Delo, 1965, 1984 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 46)
  - Press: Yugoslavia: Politika, 1935-1990 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 47)
  - Press: Yugoslavia: Praxis, 1965-1976 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 48)
  - Press: Yugoslavia: Put, 1966 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 49)
  - Press: Yugoslavia: Services and Syndicates, 1955-1991 (Offsite-box 2475, Folder 50)
  - Press: Zaire, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 1)
  - Press: Zaire: A-Z, 1975-1978, 1991 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 2)
  - Press: Zaire: Services and Syndicates, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 3)
  - Press: Zambia, 1953-1991 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 4)
  - Press: Zanzibar, 1964, 1987 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 5)
  - Press: Zimbabwe, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 6)
  - Press: Zimbabwe Rhodesia, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 7)
  - Songs, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 8-9)
  - Songs: Aa-Az, 1934-2000 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 10-17)
  - Songs: Alexander's Ragtime Band, 1958, 1983-1989 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 18)
  - Songs: All the Things You Are, 1960 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 19)
  - Songs: Amazing Grace, 1972-1990 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 20)
  - Songs: America the Beautiful, 1933-1990 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 21)
  - Songs: American Pie, 1972-1984 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 22)
  - Songs: Anthems, 1933-1993 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 23)
  - Songs: Anthems: A-C, 1932-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 24-26)
  - Songs: Anthems: China, 1939-1986 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 27)
  - Songs: Anthems: Congo, Belgium, 1959-1974 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 28)
  - Songs: Anthems: D-F, 1954-1979 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 29-31)
  - Songs: Anthems: France, 1932-1992, undated (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 32)
  - Songs: Anthems: G, 1931, 1965-1975 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 33)
  - Songs: Anthems: Germany, 1932-1993 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 34)
  - Songs: Anthems: Ghana, 1957-1965 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 35)
  - Songs: Anthems: Great Britain, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 36)
  - Songs: Anthems: H-I, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 37-38)
  - Songs: Anthems: India, 1938-1949 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 39)
  - Songs: Anthems: International, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 40)
  - Songs: Anthems: J-M, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 41-44)
  - Songs: Anthems: Malaya, 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 45)
  - Songs: Anthems: N, 1934-1982, undated (Offsite-box 2476, Folder 46)
  - Songs: Anthems: O-U, 1933-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 1-7)
  - Songs: Anthems: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1932-1991, undated (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 8)
  - Songs: Anthems: United Arab Republics, 1953-1965 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 9)
  - Songs: Anthems: United States, 1940-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 10)
  - Songs: Anthems: United States: Municipal Songs, 1966-1985 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 11)
  - Songs: Anthems: United States: Star Spangled Banner, 1930-1991 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 12-15)
  - Songs: Anthems: V-Z, 1933-1983, undated (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 16-18)
    There are no folders for letters W or X.
  - Songs: April in Paris, 1941-1953, 1984 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 19)
  - Songs: April in Portugal, 1957 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 20)
  - Songs: Around the World in Eighty Days, 1963 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 21)
  - Songs: Associations, 1946-1991 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 22)
  - Songs: Auld Lang Syne, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 23)
  - Songs: Autumn Leaves, 1955-1957, 1981 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 24)
  - Songs: Baa-Bz, 1935-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 25-35)
  - Songs: Ballad of the Green Berets, 1966-1989 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 36)
  - Songs: Ballads, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 2477, Folder 37-38)
  - Songs: Ballads, 1936-1960 (Offsite-box 2478, Folder 1)
  - Songs: Battle Hymn of the Republic, 1937-1986 (Offsite-box 2478, Folder 2)
  - Songs: Battle of New Orleans, 1959 (Offsite-box 2478, Folder 3)
  - Songs: Blue Skies, 1953, 1983 (Offsite-box 2478, Folder 4)
  - Songs: Body and Soul, 1953-1983 (Offsite-box 2478, Folder 5)
  - Songs: Ca-Cz, 1937-1993 (Offsite-box 2478, Folder 6-9)
  - Songs: Campaign, 1934-1993 (Offsite-box 2478, Folder 10-12)
  - Songs: Catches, 1963 (Offsite-box 2478, Folder 13)